Cass 你在吗
Cass, are you there.
Sammy受伤了
Sammy's hurt.
伤得很严重
He's hurt pretty bad.
我知道你以为生你气
I know you think that I'm pissed at you.
Cass 我们可以谈谈吗
Cass, can we talk.
你不能留下
You can't stay.
我不在乎天使坠落
But I don't care that the angels' fell.
所以 不管你做了什么
So whatever you did.
我不知道他要
I didn't know he was gonna cast.
把天使清出天堂
The angels out of heaven.
Matatron 是上帝的书记员
Metatron, he's the scribe of the God.
根本就没有试炼
There were never trials.
只是一个咒语而已
This is a spell.
他拿走了我的荣光
He took my grace.
我是凡人了
That's why I am human.
都没关系
It doesn't matter.
我们会解决的
Hey, we'll work it out.
这是预言石板
It's a tablet.
你只需要翻译就好
Now translate.It's what you do.
Kevin 你是上主的先知
Kevin, you are a prophet of the Lord.
求你了 我需要你
Please man.I need you here.
如果天使来敲门
If angels come a-knocking.
让他们进来就好
Just let them all in.
干得漂亮
Beautiful, buddy.
谢了 Barth
Thank you, Barth.
是Bartholomew
It's Bartholomew.
我们坠落人间的兄弟姐妹们
Our fallen brothers and sisters are finding.
找容器的速度都比我们预想的快
Vessels faster than we'd even hoped.
这条祈祷面向所有
This one goes out to any angel.
能听到的天使
With their ears on.
我需要帮助
I need your help.
先说名字
Start with a name.
Ezekiel
Ezekiel.
我能救你弟弟
There's a chance I can fix your brother.
我治疗Sam的同时也在治疗我自己
I heal Sam while healing myself.
附身吗
A possession.
Dean 我现在一团糟 你知道
I'm a mess, Dean.You know it.
我不能让你自己承担一切
I can't let you put this on yourself.
我不会告诉他的 Dean
I wouldn't do that, Dean.
（卡瑞伯 怀俄明州）
你们不该来这里
You shouldn't be here.
我们有来这儿的权利 就像你们一样
We have just as much right to be here as you do.
兄弟
Brother.
好了
All right, girls.
都上来了吧
Everybody.
他好多了吧
So he's better.
对
Yes.
Sam的状况已经改善了很多
Sam is much improved.
我现在待不了太久了
I shouldn't be much longer now.
行了 上一周你跟我说过
Okay, you know.You said the same thing.
同样的话了
To me last week, right.
我们刚见面的时候我就说了
As I told you when we met.
需要时间
This will take time.
好吧
Okay.
那就去治他啊
Go then.Heal.
我想要我弟弟回来
I'd like my brother back, please.
Dean 我必须说
I must say, Dean.
我对你们这次的工作不满
I'm very uncomfortable with this whole trip.
调查天使 或者
Investigating crimes involving angels or anything.
调查和天使有关的事 都让Sam和我
Involving angels puts me, and therefore Sam.
- 处于危险 - 听着
- At rish - Look.
这是家族事业 Zeke
Family business, Zeke.
懂了吗
Okay.
如果我们不管
If we ignore this.
Sam会觉得不对劲
Sam's gonna think something fishy is going on.
我相信你会小心行事
Then I trust you will be discreet.
等等 如果你知道我们去哪儿
Wait, if you know where we're going.
是不是说 你又再听我们说话了
That means you've been listen in.
你 你有没有听到
Are you…are you hearing everything.
我和Sam的所有谈话
Between me and Sam.
没有
No.
就只是一两个词
Just a word here and there.
我有比偷听更重要的事
I have better things to do with my time than eavesdrop.
比如治疗你弟弟
Like heal your brother.
- 好吧 你挺好 - 我是说
- Okay, here's the thing - I mean I was gonna say.
外面好像
It seems like it's getting.
太过于平静了
A little quiet out there, you know.
天使们没动静
Like not a peep from angels.
甚至Buddy Boyle也蒸发了
Even Buddy Boyle goes off the air.
雇佣人类做天使容器了
And stops recruiting for them.
很明显 是暴风雨前的宁静
Obviously a calm before storm.
有可能
Yeah, maybe.
怎么了
What.
那个路标上写着
That sign said.
柯林斯堡 50英里
Fort Collins, fifty miles.
那又怎样
So.
可我上一次抬头看
So, last time I looked, like.
也就几秒之前
12 seconds ago.
距离柯林斯堡还有100英里
Fort Collins was a hundred miles.
行了 自从跟那位女神
Alright, man, ever since a goddess.
亲密接触过后你就这样了
Who got her hooks into you.
不 不光是因为Vesta
No, it's more than Vesta.
这种事情已经发生好几次了
I mean, this kind of thing's been happening to me.
就好像有大把时间凭空消失了
Like there're chunks of times just missing.
就像有时候 我根本不存在一样
Like there're times that I'm not here.
就像是我说过的
Well, like I've said.
没错 那些试炼 我听你说了
Yes, the trials, I know, I heard you.
上星期你就是这么解释的
I heard you when you said it the last week.
还有上上星期 上上上星期
And the week before that and the week before that.
是啊
Yeah.
就是因为那些试炼啊
Because…damn straight the trials.
它们挖空了你
They wacked you, man.
你还没完全恢复过来 明白吗
You're not in the warp speed yet, okay.
但你会好起来的
But you will be.
我会骗你吗
Would I lie.
你们已经有人来了
Ah, one of your guys is here already.
他们是我同事
Ah, my colleagues.
探员
Agent.
Cass
Cass.
你来这儿干什么
What the hell are you doing.
你给我的警徽我还留着
I still have that badge you gave me.
嗯
Yeah.
你来这儿干什么
What the hell are you doing.
新闻里播了这些凶杀
Murders were all over the news.
我想 我应该能帮上忙
I thought I might be of help.
是的 但是Cass
Yes, but Cass.
你知道这是跟天使有关的 对吧
You know this is an angels situation, right.
我是说 你离开我们不就是因为
I mean you left that night because angels were.
- 天使到处追捕你吗 - 对啊
- On your ass - Yeah.
然后你有了新的生活
And you were living the life, you know.
你远离了这一切
Early retirement.
在便利店里工作
Working your way up the gas-n-sip ladder.
如果天使在互相残杀
If angels are slaughtering one another.
我必须想尽办法帮忙
I have to do what I can to help.
这是我们愿意冒的风险
This is a risk we should be willing to take.
你们说呢
Don't you think.
嘿
Hey.
- Cass又回来了 - 认真的吗
- Cass is back in town - Seriously.
你是不是 他是不是真那么说了
Did you…did he just say that.
这些天使
These angels, they were.
被屠杀
Butchered.
手段相当惨烈
Much more violence than was required.
肯定不止一个人干的
Definitely more than one killers to pull this off.
职业杀手吗 Bartholomew团队吗
Hit squad?Bartholomew's people.
Bartholomew分队是我们知道的
Well, Bartholomew has a faction we know about.
也可能是一个我们完全不认识的
But this could be somebody else entirely we don't know.
不管是谁
Well, whoever it is.
我们都会找到他
We'll find them.
我们
真是 太棒了
It's…great.
晚上好 Malachi
Good evening, Malachi.
他在哪
Where is he.
Bartholomew今晚会很忙
Bartholomew is quite busy tonight.
有那么一大批拥护者
With such a large following.
我的责任真重大啊
Well, the responsibilities are enormous.
我要求跟最高领导人谈话
I called for a top-level summit.
没时间理他的小罗喽
I don't deal with hand maidens.
我会向Bartholomew传达你的想法的
I'll convey your thoughts to Bartholomew.
他会为他的无礼后悔的
He'll regret the disrespect.
你跟我提无礼 Malachi
You speak of disrespect, Malachi.
经过前两天的血洗之后
After the bloodbath two nights ago.
Bartholomew公然攫取力量
Bartholomew's naked grab for power was nothing.
根本毫无尊重可言
But disrespect.
他和我其实都想要同样的东西
He and I ultimately want the same thing.
从Metatron那里夺回天堂
The only way we can take the heaven back.
只有一种方法
From Metatron.
就是联手
Is to unite.
如果Bartholomew想要避免这次你死我活的战争
And if Bartholomew wants avoid all-out warfare on earth.
他必须亲自跟我谈条件
He'll meet personally with me negotiate terms.
不好意思 我忘了早点说了
I'm sorry, I should've mentioned earlier.
Bartholomew让我告诉你
Bartholomew said to tell you.
他不跟街头混混谈条件
He doesn't negotiate with street thugs.
说完了吗
Are we done here.
说完了
Yes, we are.
好戏刚开始
And so it begins.
能再呆在一起真好
It is so good being together again.
这是我作为人类的第一杯啤酒
You know, it's my first beer as a human.
我希望我可以 加入你们
I hope it's okay…me joining you.
为什么不行
Why wouldn't it be okay.
Cass 你确定你要回来
You know, Cass, are you sure you're ready to.
参与这些事情吗
Jump back into all this.
我看你好像已经
I mean, it seemed to me like.
过上安稳日子了
You'd actually found some peace.
你曾经告诉过我
You once told me.
不是你选择要做什么 而是命运选择你
You don't choose what you do, it chooses you.
我不能置身事外
I'm a part of this.
不管愿不愿意
Like it or not.
好吧 这样的话 我们必须找出
All right, well, then in that case, we have to figure out.
我们在对付谁
Who are we up against.
他们想干嘛
What do they want.
还有怎么阻止他们
And how do we stop them.
Bartholomew想要重置Metatron的咒语
Bartholomew wants to reverse Metatron's spell.
推测他是想要夺回天堂
Presumably to retake heaven.
一旦他的拥护者足够庞大
Once his following is large enough.
这是April说的
That's according to April.
和你滚床单的那个死神
The Reaper you banged.
对 你戳死的那个
Yeah, and you stabbed.
她好性感
Yeah, she was hot.
很性感 也很体贴
So hot…and very nice.
一直到她开始拷问我
Up to the point she started torturing me.
嗯 不是每次艳遇都是完美的
Yeah, well, not every hookup's perfect.
好吧 我再去拿几瓶酒
All right, I'm gonna get us another round.
别 我去吧
Nah, I'll get it.
我从没做过这个
I've never done this before.
一杯倒啊 这哥们
One beer, he's hammered.
天啊
Oh boy.
好吧 你说你要怎么办
Well, what are you going to do about this.
关于Cass吗
About Cass.
他就像指示灯 Dean
He is a beacon, Dean.
吸引每一个天使从千里外到我们这里来
Pulling every angel from miles down on ours heads.
行了 Zeke 老实交代
All right, you know what, Zeke.Level with me.
你到底在害怕什么
What is it that you're so afraid of.
我告诉过你了
I told you.
当我选择回应你的祈祷 治愈Sam的时候
When I chose to answer your prayers and heal Sam.
我已经选好了立场
I chose sides.
意味着在某些天使眼里 我是不待见的
That means I'm not in good standing with certain angels.
那好 你知道吗
Okay, you know what.
Cass在任何一个天使眼里 都不待见
Cass isn't in good standing with any angel.
但是现在他出现在这里
All right?But here he is.
上了贼船
Ass on the line.
坚持在前线战斗
Fighting the fight.
你怎么就那么特殊呢
So tell me what makes you so special.
来吧 三瓶啤酒
Here we go, three brewskies.
我去车里拿点东西
I'm going to get something out of the car.
我等你等好久了
Well, I'm really looking forward to this.
你说什么
Excuse me.
拜托
Oh, please.
我知道你的真面目
I know who you really are.
反正不是Ezekiel
And it isn't Ezekiel.
我注意到
I um…I noticed you look.
每次Sam提到我离开的时候 你有些尴尬
Kind of uncomfortable whenever Sam mentions my leaving.
他不知道是你让我离开的吗
Doesn't he know that you told me to leave.
事情是这样的
Here is the deal.
Sam通过了那些试炼
Look, when Sam was doing the trials.
为了封印地狱 把自己身体搞砸了
To seal up hell, it messed him up, okay.
第三个试炼差点弄死他
The third one nearly killed him.
如果我继续让他完成试炼 他就死了
If I'd let him finish, it would have.
他状态还是非常糟
He's still messed up bad.
你说那个叫Ezekiel的天使治愈了他
You said the angel Ezekiel, helped heal him.
我必须尽我所能救他
Well, I got to do anything I can to get him back.
如果这意味着我们必须暂时
Now, if that means that we keep our distance from you.
远离你 那么
For a little while, then.
我别无选择
I don't have a choice.
我知道这样不好 但是我也没得选
I don't feel good about it, but I don't have a choice.
你能帮我们真的太好了
It's great to have your help, Cass.
但是我们不能一起奋战
Okay, but we just can't work together.
放心吧 我不是来揭穿你的
Relax, I'm not here to out you.
我只是好奇为什么选择Ezekiel
But I'm curious why Ezekiel.
他们说他很优秀
They say he is a good.
是个可敬的天使
And honorable angel.
他们说的都不是你
Everything they say you are not.
我懂你的意思 Gadriel
I see your point, Gadriel.
关于我的那些事情 都不是真的
The stories about me, they are not true.
而你 却在数不清的日日夜夜里
And yet you spent countless thousands of years.
被困在天堂最阴暗的地牢里
Locked in the heaven's darkest dungeon.
现在你藏在一个人类的身体里
And now you're hiding in this human.
装作是Ezekiel
Posing as Ezekiel.
悲剧啊
Tragic.
他有多不忍心囚禁你 你知道吗
It broke his heart to lock you away, you know.
你曾经是他最信任的人
You were God's most trusted.
所以他才选择你守护伊甸园
That's why he chose you to protect the garden.
你唯一的职责就是不让邪恶入侵
Your one task was to keep evil from entering.
阻止其污染他最珍贵的产物 人类
From befouling his cherished creation, mankind.
但是你失败了
And you failed him.
不是我的错
Not my doing.
不管怎么样 大蛇钻进去了
Well, for whatever reason, the serpent entered.
地球被邪恶诅咒了
The earth is cursed with evil.
必须有人受到责罚
Someone had to be blamed.
你到底想从我这里得到什么 Metatron
What is it you want of me, Metatron.
只是做你的朋友而已
Just to be your friend.
像我们从前一样
You and I go back a long way.
我才是那个放你出来的人
I was actually the one who freed you.
你吗
You.
是我让所有的天使坠落
I was the one who caused all the angels to fall.
包括被囚禁的那些
Including the imprisoned ones.
不客气
You're welcome.
天堂里没有天使 一个都没有
No angels are in heaven, none at all.
没有 一开始我还以为我会高兴
No, and you know, at first I thought I would love it.
可是那地儿太大了
But it is a big place.
我一个人在那里太没意思了
My solitude is getting tedious.
所以呢
And so.
所以
新计划
Plan B.
重建天堂
Rebuild heaven.
像上帝原来想要的那样
As the place God had envisioned it.
仅有几个精心挑选的天使
Only with a handpicked few.
不要那些腐败官僚 像Bartholomew那样的
No more anemic functionaries like Bartholomew.
没有那些呆天使
And no more stupid angels.
可以有几个好玩的
Maybe some funny ones.
你曾是他最信任的 Gadriel
You were his most trusted, Gadriel.
你也想赢回你的荣誉
You want to take back your reputation.
你想重新掌管天堂吗
You want to reclaim the heaven that was.
我们可以联手
We could do this together.
有Cass的消息吗
Any word from Cass.
还没有
Nothing yet.
我们难道不应该担心一下他吗
And we're not worried about him.
他这次
That he just.
又一声不吭的自己跑了
Took off like that again.
他一般不会单独做这样的事情的
I mean it's not like he does this kind of stuff alone.
这是他自己的选择
It's what he wanted, honestly.
自从他变成人类之后
Look, man, he's been all over the map.
就一直到处转悠
Since he got his wings clipped.
你有什么发现吗
What do you got.
讣告
Obituaries.
是那些骑手之一吗
That one of the bikers.
是的
Yeah.
这个人叫Red Dawg
His name is Red Dawg.
当然了
Of course he was.
不是你想的那样
It's not what you think.
这人是个恋家的好男人
Look, he's a family guy.
家庭教师协会的带头人 在圣诞派对扮圣诞老人
Big in the PTA, he played Santa at Christmas parties.
难不成是某一天他脑子一抽就加入骑行帮了
So what, just one day he up and joined a biker gang.
不 他几年前就加入了
No, he did that years ago.
听这个 这很奇怪
Get this, this is weird.
看
Look.
这些都是受害者 对吧
These are all the victims, right.
他们是一起接受的洗礼
They were all baptized together.
洗礼
Baptized.
是的 他们是个重生的骑行帮
Yeah, they were a born-again biker gang.
好吧 这可不是什么寻常事儿
Well, that's not something you hear everyday.
确实不是
No, it's not.
等等 把这儿放大
Wait, make that bigger.
Bolye兄弟
Boyle's Boys.
Bolye是指牧师Buddy Boyle吗
Boyle as in reverend Buddy Boyle.
听这个
Listen to this.
Red Dawg的妻子说他丈夫是个有信仰的人
Red Dawg's widow said he was always religious.
就在他去世前一个星期
But a week before he died.
他参加了一个教会成员聚会
He came home from a prayer meeting.
整个人改头换面
And was a changed man.
内心充满神圣的荣耀
Filled with divine glory.
这么说又和Boyle有关
So Boyle is at it again.
诱导人们自愿当天使的皮囊
Selling folks on being meatsuits for angels.
只不过这次听众范围缩小了 是吗
Just what talking to a smaller groups now.
我不知道 有可能
I don't know, maybe.
一次性帮助太多天使
Softening up thousands at a time.
他就没法控制得到肉身的是哪些天使了
He wasn't able to control what angels got let in.
但用这种方式
This way.
只要Boyle还在那儿散播他的理论
Bartholomew's followers can jump in.
Bartholomew的追随者
Just as soon as Bolye.
就能轻而易举的找到肉身
Still does this thing.
这么说Red Dawg他们
So Red Dawg and his guys.
都是Bartholomew的人
Were Bartholomew people.
是啊 他们本人早就被杀害了
Yeah, they got slaughtered.
换句话说 现在的情况更糟糕
Which means that this new group is even worse.
我就知道天使们都是混蛋
Haven't I always said that angels are dicks.
非常荣幸能有机会
And I so appreciate the opportunity.
在圣经学习小组致辞
To address your bible study group.
我钦佩你们的热情 精力和投入
I admire your passion, your energy, your devotion.
毫无疑问你们就是
You are exactly what God and his angels.
上帝和天使们心中的人选
Have in mind for the crusade.
现在 全体起立
Now, rise.
拉起你们的双手
Join hands.
大家一起
All of you.
感受从天堂传递出的无限爱意
Feel the heavenly host reach out to embrace you.
并回赠你们的爱意
Embrace them back.
天使们只想感受到你们的爱
The angels want nothing more than to feel your love.
欢迎他们进驻你们的心灵
Welcome them into your hearts.
让他们进来
Let them in.
以Malachi之名
In the name of Malachi.
让他们进来
Let them in.
老实说 我一直都没有习惯他们
Frankly, I never got used to them.
我在他们之中生活了千年之久
I lived among them for centuries.
我不得不隐居起来才能保持神志清醒
I had to isolate myself to keep sane.
人类确实有混乱无序的一面 Metatron
Humans do seem chaotic, Metatron.
这也让他们变得迷人 但是
Which makes them fascinating, but.
那些潮水般的情感 天呐
All that emotion, geez.
还有他们浪费掉的能力 真是
And the wasted energy, it's just.
让人心力交瘁
Exhausting.
我懂
I know.
Sam Winchester
Sam Winchester.
简直就是一团糟 更别提他的哥哥
It is a mess in here, and the brother.
我都不知从何说起
I do not know where to start.
我能让你脱离他们
I can free you from them.
不论是人类还是天使
From all of them.
你想成为新天堂的主人
You intend to be the ruler of this new heaven.
我说的对吗
Am I correct.
这是种责任
It is a burdon.
我有义务承担
I feel I must accept.
Metatron 这样你不就变成上帝了吗
Metatron, but does that not make you God.
上帝只是个名字
Semantics.
我不觉得我能取代这个名字
I don't know that I'd take on that name.
绝对不会
Necessarily, no.
当一切大功告成之时 可以叫我
When the time comes, we'll call me.
X
X.
你和我
You and I.
咱们能重建天堂 Gadriel
We can have paradise again, Gadriel.
好吧
Okay.
我对这一头的程序一点都不熟
I'm unfamiliar with this end of the process.
当然 有可能根本没有人在听
Of course, no one may be listening.
但是我真的需要帮助
But I do need assistance.
我现在遇到了一个死胡同
I have questions and there seem to be no answers.
如果不是走投无路
I wouldn't presume to ask for help.
我不会向你们祈祷的
If I weren't desperate.
但我真的需要帮助
But I need help.
我迷失了方向
I'm lost.
需要你们的指引
I need your guidance.
拜托了
Please.
听听我的祈祷吧
Hear my prayer.
我不知道人类是怎么做到的
I don't know how humans do it.
试试插一下插头
Try pluging it in.
虽然这并不是你想要的答案
Surely that wasn't the answer you were seeking.
你是个天使
You're an angel.
Muriel
Muriel.
这衣服不是我自己选的
I didn't pick the outfit.
Castiel
Castiel.
不 等等 请听我说完
No, wait, please just hear me out.
我不能让别人知道我在跟你说话
It can't be known that I even spoke to you.
我只需要一点时间
I just need a moment.
不
No.
拜托了
Please.
我只想了解一下情况
I just need information.
Dean 也许根本就没有解决的办法
Dean, there may be nothing in here.
Crowley说
Crowley said.
那个咒语是不可逆转的
The spell that cast down the angels was irreversible.
先不管Crowley怎么说
Well, screw Crowley.
你为什么觉得他说的是真的
Why would you think that anything he says is true.
这些字句根本解读不了
This part is nearly indecipherable.
就像是Metatron本来就不想
It was like, when Metatron wrote it down.
让人们读懂
He wanted to keep the word hidden.
包括先知
Even from prophets.
嘿
Hey.
看看这个
Check this out.
又一起天使袭击
Another angel attack.
什么 在哪儿
What, where.
犹他州
Utah.
一所学院的圣经学习小组
A college bible study group.
又一位高级别的教会女士
And their, guest speaker, some top-shelf church lady.
尸体从内部烧焦 学生们的眼睛都消失了
Insides scorched out, kids' eyes were missing.
但教会女士的眼睛还在
But not the church lady's.
这么说 她也是天使
So, she was an angel too.
有可能
Sounds like.
还有 她是教会欢乐合唱团的女高音
And she sang soprano for the, Melody Ministry glee club.
好吧
Okay.
唱诗班去表演时总是坐同一辆车
The club goes to its gigs on a bus.
所以我问过了怀俄明警方
So when I checked with the Wyoming cops.
他们的目击证人声称 在找到尸体前
They said that the witness saw the same bus.
他看见同一辆车
Leaving the biker bar not long.
从骑行者酒吧开过
Before the bodies were found.
这么说
So.
这位教会女士跟两件案子都有关系
Church lady angel was at both killings.
应该是她和她一起逃难的同伴
I'm guessing that she and whoever she's running with.
在酒吧里杀了Bartholomew的人
Killed Bartholomew's bikers at the bar and then.
然后被Bartholomew的人找上门来
Barth's boys hit her back.
就在她招收新的皮囊的时候
When she's recruiting those students to be vessels.
是啊 都是孩子
Well, a bunch of kids.
Kevin
Kevin.
时间紧迫
Clock's ticking.
假设你说的都是真的
Let's say you're telling the truth that.
Metatron真的骗了你
Metatron tricked you.
我还是应该把你交出去
I should still turn you in.
但是你不会
But you won't.
别这么肯定
Don't be so sure.
我
I.
我觉得你出于本能的信任我
I think you instinctively trust me.
我们很相似
We're similar.
我们在那些激进的团体中保持中立
We both want no part of the fanatics.
那你刚才祈祷的时候
And when you prayed.
你怎么知道来的不会是他们的人
How did you know you wouldn't get one of them.
我能屏蔽他们的追踪 而且我没有荣光了
I'm warded and my grace's gone.
所以我希望我看起来就像是
And I was hoping that I would seem like just.
随便一个绝望的人类
Another desperate human that.
不会引起那些激进团体的注意
That militants couldn't care less about.
你觉得我关心吗
And you think I care.
你来了
You're here.
你可能会了解现在的情况
You may know the situation.
Bartholomew他要血洗另一个团体
Bartholomew, he's in a blood feud with another faction.
太疯狂了
It's madness.
现在谁在对抗他
Who leads the opposition.
Malachi
Malachi.
那个无政府主义者
The anarchist.
他现在和Bartholomew平起平坐了
He has become equal with Bartholomew.
甚至更强
In some ways, worse.
但是还是有你这样
But there are still those like you.
想置身事外的
Who want to stay out of it.
越来越少了
Fewer and fewer.
两方都想
Each side is rounding up those.
拉拢中立派
Who try and stay neutral.
天使们会被折磨和杀害
Angels are being tortured and killed.
如果不发誓效忠某一方的话
If they don't pledge loyalty.
比我预想的还要糟糕
It's worse than I thought.
两方都想消灭另一方
Each side wants to crash the other.
推翻Metatron的统治 称霸天堂
Overthrow Metatron and rule heaven and.
不管谁掌管天堂 那都会是
Heaven under either of them would be.
地狱
Hell.
意外收获啊 Castiel
This is a bonus, Castiel.
我们本来是在跟踪Muriel
We're tracking Muriel.
就是她这个没骨气的反抗者
Cowardly holdout that she is.
最神奇的是
And wonder of wonders.
她竟然带我们找到了你
She led us to you.
不知情的情况下
Not knowingly.
我修正一下 在不知情的情况下
I state corrected, not knowingly.
真是愚蠢
Stupidly.
我详细地解释一下
Explain in detail.
我不知道Metatron的咒语是怎么生效的
I don't know how Metatron's spell worked.
因此 我无法协助你们逆转咒语
Therefore, I can't assist in reversing it.
我是个无辜的从犯
I was an unwitting accomplice.
受骗者
A dupe.
伟大的Castiel 被信任和重用的Castiel
The great Castiel, valued and trusted Castiel.
精英中的精英 Castiel
Top-of-the-Christmas-tree Castiel.
也只是个受骗者
No more than a dupe.
不管是被骗还是策划者 你当时是参与者
Dupe or mastermind you were inside the circle.
你知道Metatron的弱点是什么
You know where Metatron's weakness lies.
不
No.
我不知道
I don't.
Theo
Theo.
不
No.
为了你的信仰 你甘愿受苦 甚至牺牲
You'd suffer, even die for your beliefs.
我懂
I get it.
但是是Metaron
But is Metatron.
他的支持者数量已经大幅下降了
Whose poll numbers have totally tanked.
还值得你赔上性命吗
Worth your life.
更重要的是
More importantly.
Metatron值得她赔命吗
Is Metatron worth her life.
不
No.
不 她是无辜的
No, she is innocent.
你别动她
You leave her alone.
我没想碰她
I have no intentions on touching her.
美德自身就是惩罚
Virtue is its own punishment.
等等 不要
Wait, no.
天使 屠杀天使
Angels butchering angels.
我们已经沦落至此了吗
Is this what we've become.
跟随你的脚步而已 Castiel
Just following your example, Castiel.
你在天堂杀了多少天使
How many did you kill in heaven.
在他们坠落的时候又杀了多少
How many in the fall.
哦 你还不知道啊
Oh, you didn't know.
无数的天使在坠落中死去
A host of angels died when they fall.
Azriel，Sophia
Azriel, Sophia.
Ezekiel
Ezekiel.
还不只是死去这么简单
Died doesn't even describe it.
更像是毁灭
Devastation.
翅羽粉碎 无法言说的痛苦
Wings shredded, unspeakable agony.
拜你所赐
At your hands.
所以我觉得
So I think.
你应该愿意提供所有你知道的信息
You would want to provide any information you have.
考虑考虑吧
Considering.
好吧
All right.
我把你交给拷问大师了
I'll leave you in the hands of the artist.
我不在乎还剩下什么
I don't care what's left.
不用祈求仁慈
Don't ask for mercy.
我没有仁慈
There is none.
我给你最后一个机会结束这一切
I'll give you one last chance for this to end.
让我死个痛快吧
Give me a quick death.
我要你去和Metatron谈谈
I need you to speak to Metatron.
每个人都知道你的影响力
Everyone knows you have influence.
他会听你的
He'll listen to you.
让他带我重归天堂
Ask him to raise me to heaven.
你能做到的 Castiel
You can do this, Castiel.
我会成为Metatron的战士
I'll be a soldier for Metatron.
对他言听计从
Do anything he wants.
你 你不是效忠于Malachi吗
You, you serve Malachi.
我本以为他能解决问题 结果发现他是个疯子
I thought he was the answer, but he's crazy.
怎么 你现在才发现吗
What, are you, noticing this now.
你刚才似乎很享受给他做苦力
You are more than willing to do his dirty work.
我不得不这么做
I doid what I had to.
你之前确信他能打败Bartholomew
But you were sure he would defeat Bartholomew.
但是没人能逃过这场战争
But no one will survive this war.
所以你想去天堂旁观这一出闹剧
So you prefer to sit it out in heaven.
我可以向他要求恢复你的荣光
I could talk to him about restoring your grace.
的确
Well, it's…it's ture.
Metatron和我有工作上的联系
Metatron and I do have a working relationship.
我就知道
I know it.
你很聪明 Theo
You're clever, Theo.
你是盟友
You're allies.
他也确实需要一名出色的战士
And he could use a skilled soldier.
像你这样的
Like yourself.
我不确定
But I don't know.
我很擅长团队协作 Castiel
I'm a team player, Castiel.
好吧
All right, well.
我需要一点时间来联系他
I'll need a moment to make contact.
你有我需要的东西
And you have something that I'll need.
什么都行
Anything.
不
No.
嘿 看到Sam了吗
Hey, seen Sam.
他出去了
He went out.
哪里
Where.
不知道
I don't know.
你发现他最近总是这样玩消失了吗
You notice he's doing that a lot.
喂
Yeah.
Dean 时间紧迫 听好了
Dean, I don't have a lot of time, so listen.
反对派天使的领袖名叫Malachi
The leader of the opposition is an angel named Malachi.
你怎么知道的
How did you know that.
他抓住了我 我
He had me, I.
我被拷打了
I was tortured.
但是我逃走了
But I got away.
怎么逃走
How.
我不得不这么做
I…I did what I had to.
变成跟他们一样
Became what they've become.
野蛮人
A barbarian.
你说什 Cass 你在哪里
What are you…Cass, where are you.
我还是离开你们比较好
It's better I stay away.
现在他们更想要抓我了
They're gonna want me even more now.
我会没事的
And I'm gonna be all right, I.
我的荣光恢复了
Got my grace back.
本质上说不是我的荣光 不过
Well, not mine per se, but.
也有用
It'll do.
等等 你恢复了吗
Wait, you…you're back.
你力量又回来了吗
You got your mojo.
我也不确定
I'm not sure.
但我现在是天使了
But I'm an angel.
你就没有犹豫一下什么的吗
And you're okay with that.
如果要开战 我必须全面备战
If we're going to war, I need to be ready.
- Cass - Dean
- Cass - Dean.
还有一件事
There's more.
什么事
What.
你不是说一个叫Ezekiel的天使
Didn't you say Sam was healed.
在帮Sam疗伤吗
By an angel named Ezekiel.
是啊 怎么了
Uh, yeah, why.
Ezekiel死了
Ezekiel is dead.
- 什么 - 他在天使坠落的时候已经死了
- What - He died when the angels fell.
我现在就要咒语
I need the spell ASAP.
人人都说要咒语
Everyone always needs a spell.
一直都说现在就要
And it's always ASAP.
好吧 听着
All right, listen to me.
天使不能被其他人驱逐
An angel can't be expelled by another human.
只能被宿主驱逐 对吧
Only by the host, right.
但是如果 有方法能减弱天使的力量
But what if, there's a way to power down the angels.
短时间内无法恢复
So that it wasn't in charge for a few seconds.
- 什么 - 例如
- What - For instant, if.
假设我想要跟他的肉身本人说话 但
Hypothetically, I want to speak with the vessel, but.
不想让寄住在肉身里的天使听到
Not had the squatter listen in.
为什么
Why.
为什么 Kevin
Why, Kevin.
现在有这么多被附身的人类
We've got tons of possessed humans out there.
懂吗
You with me.
当天使们互相残杀的时候
And when the angels kill each other off.
作为宿主的人类才是最大的受害者
The humans are taking it in the teeth.
所以如果我想提供信息给肉身本人
So what if I wanted to clue a human in.
让他或她把天使赶出来
So that he or she could spit the angel out.
这是一件好事 对吧
That would be a good thing, right.
- 是吧 - 行
- Uh, yeah - Okay.
开始翻译石板 行动
So, hit the tablet.Let's go.
- 现在吗 - 昨天 灰姑娘
- Now? - Yesterday, Cinderella.
Metatron 我一直在考虑
I've been thinking this over, Metatron.
我会加入你作为副手
I'll join you at second in command.
非常好 Gadriel
Bravo, Gadriel.
此次行动将会抹去诸世纪来
This move will erase the mark.
你倍受鄙视的罪名
That has hounded you through the centuries.
天堂会恢复
Heaven will be restored.
你也会变成最受人尊敬的英雄
As will your reputation as one of its greatest heroes.
感谢你给我这次机会
I thank you for this opportunity.
但还有一件事
There's just one more thing.
什么事
Yes.
我必须确认你是忠诚于我的
I need to be sure of your fidelity.
我已经向你示忠了
You have it.
不 我是要非常确定
No, I mean really sure.
外面还有
We have enemies who pose.
可能威胁到我们行动的敌人
An imminent threat to our effort.
他们必须被中和掉
They must be neutralized.
杀死他们吗
Slain.
可以这么说
In a word.
那不是我的作风
That…that is not who I am.
是啊 这是你任务清单上的第一个名字
Yeah, here's the first name on your to-do list.
是时候作出决定了
Decide.
所以我们刚才画的那玩意儿
All right, so this masterpiece we just painted.
会起作用的 对吗
It's gonna work, right.
这个符咒应该
The sigils're supposed to.
可以削弱天使的力量
Briefly hobble the possessing angel.
如果消息准确的话
If the info is correct.
等等 什么意思
Wait, what.
时间太短了 我从石板上找到的信息很有限
I only had time to get a little from tablet.
剩下的是从学者的古籍上找到的
The rest came from the old Men of Letters' book.
只要你的血触碰到那个符咒
As soon as your blood touches the ignition sigil.
咒语就能起作用
The spell kicks in.
Dean 发生什么事了
Dean, what's going on.
我都跟你说了
I told you.
理论上你是告诉我了
You told me theoretically.
Dean 我们在储藏室里画了符咒
Dean, we just painted sigils in the storeroom.
到底怎么回事
What the hell.
你必须相信我 好吗
You've got to trust me, okay.
我会把我能透露的都告诉你
Trust that I told you everything that I can for now.
做得到吗
Can you do that.
我一直都相信你
I always trust you.
但是每一次都搞砸了
It always ends up screwed.
拜托 每一次吗 不是每一次
Come on, always, not always.
嘿 你去哪了
Hey, where have you been.
买啤酒
Hey, beer run.
去好久啊
Long beer run.
能聊聊吗
Can we talk.
嗯 可以
Yeah, sure.
是有什么重要的事儿吗
This sounds serious.
怎么回事
What's going on.
你在干什么
What are you doing.
我没有那么多时间解释了
I got to tell you some stuff fast.
你听了会很生气的
It's gonna piss you off.
好吧
Okay.
那些试炼真的让你状况很糟糕
Those trials really messed you up.
- 嗯 我知道 - 不 你不知道
- Yes, I know that - No, you don't.
我说的状态糟糕是差点死去
I mean messed you up like almost dead.
不再有生日 尘归尘
No more birthdays, dust to dust.
我不能看着你死去 所以我做了一次决定
That messed me up, so I made a move, okay.
我在没有跟你商量的情况下 做了艰难的决定
A tough move about you without talking it over.
因为当时你处于昏迷
Because you were at a coma.
什么 什么时候
What?When.
你在医院里
You were in the hospital.
他们说你快要死了
Okay, they said you were going to die.
你做了什么
What did you do.
我让天使附身
I let an angel in.
在谁身上
In what.
你身上
In you.
他说他能够治愈你 他确实做到了
He said he can heal you and he is.
他现在还在我身上吗
He's still in me.
等等 不可能的 Dean 这不可能发生的
Wait, it's impossible, Dean.That couldn't happen.
我从未邀请他附我身上
I never invited him in.
我骗你让你说了愿意 Sam
I tricked you into saying yes, Sam.
这是唯一的办法
It seemed like the only way.
又这样
So, again.
你认为我无法处理
You thought I couldn't handle something.
- 所以你就自作主张 - 我不得不这么做
- So you took over - No, I did what I have to do.
你是不会答应这样做的
You would've never agreed to it.
而且你会死去的
And you would've died.
或者至少让我选择一下也好啊
Or maybe I would've liked the choice at least.
晚一点我们再讨论这个
We can do this later.
你想怎么打我都行
You, you can kick my ass all you want.
现在我们有更严重的问题要解决
Right now we got bigger problems.
严重的问题
Bigger.
那天使说谎了
The angel lied to me.
他不是他口中的那个人
Okay, he's not who he said he was.
他说他的名字叫Ezekiel
He said his name was Ezekiel.
据Cass说的 他是个好人
Cool guy according to Cass.
但是他不是Ezekiel
But he's not Ezekiel.
那他是谁
Well, then who is he.
我不知道
I don's know.
显然Ezekiel已经死了
Apparently Ezekiel is dead.
不管他是谁 只要他愿意
Whoever this guy is can end you in a heartbeat.
他可以随时要你的命 你必须驱逐他
If he wants to, so you've got to dump him.
你听到我所说的吗
Are you hearing what I'm saying.
我觉得你现在已经恢复得差不多了
I think you're well enough now.
但是你现在必须驱逐他
But you got to expel him.
Sam Sam
Sam, Sam.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 Sam
Hey, Sam.
你有察觉到
Hey, do you notice anything.
最近Dean有些反常吗
A little bit off about Dean lately.
私下说 我有点担心他了
Between you and me, I'm a little bit worried about him.
不用担心Dean
Don't worry about Dean.
他会没事的
Dean will be fine.
不
No.
不 Kevin
No, no, Kevin.
Sam
Sam.
Sam已经不在了
There's no more Sam.
不过我觉得我掩饰得很好
But I played him convincingly I thought.
你怎么
How did you.
今晚我听到你跟Kevin Tran的对话
I heard you talked with Kevin Tran tonight.
理论上你是告诉我了
You told me theoretically.
Dean 我们在储藏室里画了符咒
Dean, we just painted sigil in the storeroom.
怎么回事
What the hell.
你必须相信我 好吗
You've got to trust me, okay.
我会把我能透露的都告诉你
Trust that I told you everything that I can for now.
做得到吗
Can you do that.
只要改动了符咒
Alter a sigil.
哪怕只有一点儿
Even the slightest.
就能改变咒语
Alter the spell.
对于Kevin 我感到抱歉
Sorry about Kevin.
但终归
But ultimately.
我这么做的出发点是好的
It's for the best.
我不得不这么做
I did what I had to.
Kevin
Kevin.